Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪When your lies and indifference♪
♪عندما تكذب ولا مبالاتك♪
♪Pierce my heart and shatter it♪
♪اخترق قلبي وحطمه♪
♪All my piety and persistence♪
♪كل تقواي ومثابرتي♪
♪Are torn apart, turning into bubbles in the air♪
♪تتمزق وتتحول إلى فقاعات في الهواء♪
♪When my fairy tale is broken by you♪
♪عندما تحطم حكايتي الخيالية بسببك♪
♪Turning into nightmares that haunt me♪
♪تتحول إلى كوابيس تطاردني♪
♪I decide to break free from your shackles♪
♪قررت أن أتحرر من قيودك♪
♪No longer swallowing the poison apple♪
♪ لم يعد يبتلع تفاحة السم ♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
♪I burn the fairy tale, rewrite the role♪
♪أحرق الحكاية الخيالية، وأعيد كتابة الدور♪
♪Reborn as a resolute me♪
♪ولدت من جديد كشخصية حازمة♪
♪I have broken free from your shackles♪
♪لقد تحررت من قيودك♪
♪Throwing away that poison apple♪
♪رمي تلك التفاحة المسمومة♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
[Love Conspiracy]
[مؤامرة الحب]
[Adapted from Enhenzhai's novel, Madam, No Mercy for Scum]
[مقتبس من رواية إينهينزهاي، سيدتي، لا رحمة للحثالة]
[Episode 12]
[الحلقة 12]
[People's Court]
[محكمة الشعب]
Mr. Chen,
السيد تشين،
with the evidence we have now,
مع الأدلة التي لدينا الآن،
what are the chances of winning?
ما هي فرص الفوز؟
Mr. Wei,
السيد وي،
to be honest,
صراحة،
not very promising,
ليس واعدًا جدًا،
but we'll do our best.
ولكننا سنبذل قصارى جهدنا.
Wei Ziming.
وي زيمينج.
This is Bai Xue, who impersonated Zhizhi in the video.
هذا هو باي شيو، الذي انتحل شخصية تشيزي في الفيديو.
She is willing to come back to testify and surrender.
وهي مستعدة للعودة للشهادة والاستسلام.
You brought her back?
هل ارجعتها؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Ji searched the entire Milan
قام جي بالبحث في جميع أنحاء ميلانو
to find Bai Xue.
للعثور على باي شيويه.
Ms. Bai Xue,
السيدة باي شيويه،
do you know why we asked you
هل تعلم لماذا طلبنا منك ذلك؟
to come back?
للعودة؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Mr. Ji has already explained it clearly.
لقد أوضح السيد جي الأمر بوضوح بالفعل.
I didn't know things would be so serious at that time.
لم أكن أعلم أن الأمور ستكون بهذه الخطورة في ذلك الوقت.
I was blinded by money for a moment.
لقد أعمتني الأموال للحظة.
They sent me abroad
لقد أرسلوني إلى الخارج
and even sent someone to assassinate me.
بل وأرسل شخصًا لاغتيالي.
Fortunately, Mr. Ji saved me.
لحسن الحظ، السيد جي أنقذني.
Now I am willing to come forward
الآن أنا على استعداد للتقدم إلى الأمام
to identify the murderer
لتحديد هوية القاتل
and help Ms. Song clear her name.
ومساعدة السيدة سونغ في تبرئة اسمها.
Then Ms. Bai Xue,
ثم السيدة باي شيويه،
Mr. Chen, let's go.
السيد تشين، دعنا نذهب.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Thank you for your hard work.
شكرا لك على عملك الجاد.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I did all this for Zhizhi.
لقد فعلت كل هذا من أجل Zhizhi.
Where did you find this bunch of losers?
أين وجدت هذه المجموعة من الخاسرين؟
Not only did you fail to get Ji Baijian done,
لم تفشل فقط في إنجاز Ji Baijian،
but you even let him send Bai Xue back.
لكنك سمحت له أيضًا بإرسال باي شيو مرة أخرى.
A bunch of idiots.
مجموعة من البلهاء.
I said let Bai Xue disappear.
قلت دع باي شيو يختفي.
Don't you understand what that means?
ألا تفهم ماذا يعني ذلك؟
We underestimated Ji Baijian.
لقد قللنا من تقدير جي بيجيان.
We didn't expect him to survive in Italy
لم نتوقع أن يبقى على قيد الحياة في إيطاليا
and even save Bai Xue.
وحتى انقاذ باي شيويه.
Alright, forget it, stop talking.
حسنًا، انسى الأمر، توقف عن الكلام.
It's really annoying.
إنه أمر مزعج حقًا.
Now Song Zhizhi is out too.
الآن Song Zhizhi خرج أيضًا.
I'm worried this matter will bring us
أنا قلق من أن هذا الأمر سيجلب لنا
a lot of unnecessary trouble.
الكثير من المتاعب غير الضرورية.
What's there to worry about?
ما الذي يدعو للقلق؟
Now, there's no evidence
الآن، لا يوجد دليل
that we're related to this matter.
أننا مرتبطون بهذه المسألة.
We just need to pin everything
نحن بحاجة فقط إلى تثبيت كل شيء
on Nie Xiaofei.
على ني شياوفى.
Dad,
أب،
this is the document I brought back from abroad.
هذه هي الوثيقة التي أحضرتها من الخارج.
There's no signature of Song Shan on it.
لا يوجد توقيع لـSong Shan عليه.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Didn't this batch of rough gemstones still
ألم تكن هذه الدفعة من الأحجار الكريمة الخام لا تزال
stay in his family for more than ten years?
البقاء في عائلته لمدة تزيد عن عشر سنوات؟
This just shows
هذا يظهر فقط
Song Shan knew these rough gemstones had an unknown origin
عرف سونغ شان أن هذه الأحجار الكريمة الخام لها أصل غير معروف
and he hid it on purpose.
وأخفى ذلك عمدا.
Dad,
أب،
I find it a bit suspicious.
أجد الأمر مشبوهًا بعض الشيء.
While I was investigating this abroad,
بينما كنت أقوم بالتحقيق في هذا الأمر في الخارج،
I was followed and attacked.
لقد تم ملاحقتي ومهاجمتي.
If the other side's target was this document,
إذا كان هدف الطرف الآخر هو هذه الوثيقة،
at that time, Song Shan
في ذلك الوقت، سونغ شان
was in a severe coma in the hospital
كان في غيبوبة شديدة في المستشفى
and Song Zhizhi was framed and taken away for investigation,
وتم إلقاء القبض على سونغ تشي تشي واقتيادها للتحقيق،
the Song family shouldn't have had the manpower
لا ينبغي لعائلة سونغ أن تمتلك القوة البشرية
to go after the document
للذهاب وراء الوثيقة
while following me.
بينما كان يتبعني.
Could there be other people involved?
هل يمكن أن يكون هناك أشخاص آخرين متورطين؟
Moreover, the Song family has been hit
علاوة على ذلك، تعرضت عائلة سونغ للضرب
one after another recently.
واحدة تلو الأخرى مؤخرًا.
Business is like a battlefield.
إن الأعمال التجارية مثل ساحة المعركة.
The Song family surely has more enemies than just us.
من المؤكد أن عائلة سونغ لديها أعداء أكثر منا.
I have to remind you.
يجب علي أن أذكرك.
Don't let your relationship with Song Zhizhi
لا تدع علاقتك مع سونغ تشيزي
affect your judgment.
تؤثر على حكمك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
you came back so soon.
لقد عدت سريعا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you scared?
هل انت خائفة؟
I've always acted
لقد كنت اتصرف دائما
openly and aboveboard.
بكل صراحة ووضوح.
What do I have to be scared of?
ما الذي يجب أن أخاف منه؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Going out to do evil again?
هل تخرج لتفعل الشر مرة أخرى؟
So you
لذا انت
call taking care of your father in the hospital
اتصل لرعاية والدك في المستشفى
doing evil.
فعل الشر.
Speaking of him, he's really pitiful.
إذا تحدثنا عنه فهو مثير للشفقة حقًا.
They say raising children is a guarantee for old age.
يقولون أن تربية الأبناء ضمان للشيخوخة.
But look at him, that's not true, right?
لكن انظر إليه، هذا ليس صحيحا، أليس كذلك؟
I need to go to the hospital to take care of my husband.
أحتاج أن أذهب إلى المستشفى لرعاية زوجي.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm the new nanny.
أنا المربية الجديدة.
You can call me Zhang.
يمكنك الاتصال بي تشانغ.
Zhang,
تشانغ،
where's Qing?
أين تشينغ؟
Qing said someone in her family is sick.
وقالت تشينغ إن أحد أفراد عائلتها مريض.
She needs to go back to take care of them.
إنها بحاجة إلى العودة للعناية بهم.
So she resigned and went home.
لذلك استقالت وذهبت إلى منزلها.
Xiaofei!
شياوفي!
Qing resigned and went home,
استقال تشينغ وذهب إلى منزله،
but I always find it strange.
ولكنني أجد الأمر غريبًا دائمًا.
I accidentally saw her sneaking around before
لقد رأيتها بالصدفة تتسلل من قبل
[Ji Baijian, Song Zhizhi] and went to a place far from home
[جي بايجيان، سونغ تشيزي] وذهب إلى مكان بعيد عن المنزل
to buy something.
لشراء شيء ما.
This is very abnormal.
هذا أمر غير طبيعي للغاية.
Sir, Madam, come and have a look.
سيدي، سيدتي، تعالوا وألقوا نظرة.
Our supermarket just opened.
لقد تم افتتاح السوبر ماركت لدينا للتو.
Buy one, get one free.
اشتري واحد واحصل على واحد مجانا.
Come, Madam, have a look.
تعالي سيدتي، ألقي نظرة.
8:00 A.M. to 8:00 P.M.,
من الساعة 8:00 صباحًا إلى 8:00 مساءً،
be sure to come and have a look.
تأكد من الحضور وإلقاء نظرة.
Great sale.
بيع رائع.
Sir, Madam, be sure to come.
سيدي، سيدتي، تأكدوا من الحضور.
Sir, Madam,
سيدي، سيدتي،
come and have a look,
تعال وألقي نظرة
Look, from 8:00 A.M. to 8:00 P.M.,
انظر، من الساعة 8:00 صباحًا إلى الساعة 8:00 مساءً،
there are special discounts.
هناك خصومات خاصة.
[Yin Qin]
[يين تشين]
[Baile Plaza] Ji, we found her.
[بيل بلازا] جي، لقد وجدناها.
They found her.
لقد وجدوها.
Let's go and have a look.
دعنا نذهب ونلقي نظرة.
To celebrate our grand opening,
للاحتفال بافتتاحنا الكبير،
all items in our supermarket are buy-one-get-one-free!
جميع العناصر في السوبر ماركت لدينا هي شراء واحد والحصول على واحد مجانًا!
Have a look. It's really nice!
ألقِ نظرة. إنه جميل حقًا!
Seriously! It's really good.
بجدية! إنه جيد جدًا.
Ms. Song.
السيدة سونغ.
Qing,
تشينغ،
let's talk.
دعونا نتحدث.
Ms. Song,
السيدة سونغ،
Ms. Song, I was wrong.
السيدة سونغ، لقد كنت مخطئا.
I'm really sorry!
انا آسف حقا!
I haven't said anything yet.
لم اقل شيئا بعد
Why are you apologizing?
لماذا تعتذر؟
Where did you go wrong?
أين أخطأت؟
Ms. Song,
السيدة سونغ،
I shouldn't have lied to you.
لا ينبغي لي أن أكذب عليك.
Saying I resigned because someone in my family was sick.
أقول أنني استقلت لأن أحد أفراد عائلتي كان مريضًا.
Then why did you?
ثم لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
Qing,
تشينغ،
I saw you walk into a car repair garage that day.
لقد رأيتك تدخل إلى مركز إصلاح السيارات في ذلك اليوم.
What did you go there for?
لماذا ذهبت إلى هناك؟
Ms. Song,
السيدة سونغ،
Ms. Song, I...
السيدة سونغ، أنا...
I...
أنا...
Let's get straight to the point.
دعونا نصل مباشرة إلى النقطة الأساسية.
We have confirmed through surveillance monitoring.
لقد تأكدنا من خلال المراقبة والرصد.
You went to the car repair garage
ذهبت إلى ورشة إصلاح السيارات
and bought lubricating oil.
واشتريت زيت التشحيم.
Mrs. Song asked me to buy the lubricating oil.
طلبت مني السيدة سونغ شراء زيت التشحيم.
She said few of her personal items were rusty
قالت إن القليل من أغراضها الشخصية كانت صدئة
and needed to apply oil.
وكانت هناك حاجة إلى تطبيق الزيت.
I thought I had a fellow villager
اعتقدت أن لدي زميلًا قرويًا
who just happened to work at the car repair garage.
الذي صادف أنه يعمل في ورشة إصلاح السيارات.
So I bought it from him.
لذلك اشتريته منه.
As for what Mrs. Song used the lubricating oil for,
أما بالنسبة لاستخدام السيدة سونغ لزيت التشحيم،
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Didn't you say
ألم تقل؟
that the lubricating oil was for rust removal.
أن زيت التشحيم كان لإزالة الصدأ.
Mrs. Song,
السيدة سونغ،
that's what Mrs. Song told me.
هذا ما قالته لي السيدة سونغ.
But she didn't ask me
لكنها لم تسألني
to remove rust from her old items.
لإزالة الصدأ من أغراضها القديمة.
As for what she used it for,
وأما ما استخدمته من أجله،
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Qing,
تشينغ،
I'll give you one last chance.
سأعطيك فرصة أخيرة.
Tell me the truth.
أخبرني الحقيقة.
Also,
أيضًا،
why was there lubricating oil
لماذا كان هناك زيت التشحيم
on the stairs where Xiaofei fell?
على الدرج حيث سقط شياوفي؟
It was...
لقد كان...
Mrs. Song who applied the oil on the stairs.
السيدة سونغ التي وضعت الزيت على الدرج.
It was on
لقد كان على
the day Xiaofei fell.
اليوم الذي سقط فيه شياوفي.
Ms. Song,
السيدة سونغ،
it really has nothing to do with me.
ليس له علاقة بي حقًا.
I didn't do anything.
لم أفعل شيئا.
I just followed Mrs. Song's request
لقد اتبعت طلب السيدة سونغ للتو
to buy the lubricating oil.
لشراء زيت التشحيم.
I didn't do anything.
لم أفعل شيئا.
Qing,
تشينغ،
you're getting more and more daring.
أنت تصبح أكثر جرأةً.
You dare to slander Mrs. Song.
أنت تجرؤ على التشهير بالسيدة سونغ.
I have evidence.
لدي دليل.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
how are your injuries?
كيف هي إصاباتك؟
You're here to gloat.
أنت هنا للتفاخر.
Yes.
نعم.
My future is ruined.
لقد دمر مستقبلي.
You don't have to pretend to be a good person here.
لا يتوجب عليك التظاهر بأنك شخص جيد هنا.
I have nothing to say to you.
ليس لدي ما أقوله لك.
I'm here today
انا هنا اليوم
to talk with you
للتحدث معك
and tell you some truths.
وأخبرك ببعض الحقائق.
Get out.
اخرج.
I don't want to see you.
لا أريد رؤيتك.
Whether you want to see me or not,
سواء كنت تريد رؤيتي أم لا،
but I hope you can think carefully.
لكن أتمنى أن تتمكن من التفكير بعناية.
In this matter,
وفي هذا الأمر،
your leg is so seriously injured,
ساقك مصابة بجروح خطيرة للغاية،
and I was detained for interrogation.
وتم احتجازي للتحقيق.
Who benefited between us?
من المستفيد بيننا؟
What exactly do you want to say?
ماذا تريد أن تقول بالضبط؟
Nie Wenzhi told the police
وقال ني Wenzhi للشرطة
that Bai Xue
أن باي شيويه
was found by your order.
تم العثور عليه بناء على طلبك.
The fake fall
السقوط المزيف
was also instigated by you.
وقد تم تحريضك عليه أيضًا.
Now you're gonna take the blame for her.
الآن سوف تتحمل اللوم عنها.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
My mom couldn't do this.
لم تتمكن أمي من فعل هذا.
You don't believe it, do you?
أنت لا تصدق ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
It was...
لقد كان...
Mrs. Song
السيدة سونغ
who applied lubricating oil on the stairs.
الذي وضع زيت التشحيم على الدرج.
It was on
لقد كان على
the day Xiaofei fell.
اليوم الذي سقط فيه شياوفي.
Do you think I'll believe you just because you randomly found someone
هل تعتقد أنني سأصدقك فقط لأنك وجدت شخصًا بالصدفة؟
to record a voice?
لتسجيل الصوت؟
Don't believe it, do you?
لا تصدق ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Or don't you want to believe it?
أم أنك لا تريد أن تصدق ذلك؟
Don't you know
ألا تعلم؟
in your own heart how you fell down the stairs?
في قلبك كيف سقطت على الدرج؟
Now Bai Xue and Qing have confessed.
الآن اعترف باي شيويه وتشينغ.
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
do you really not know
هل حقا لا تعرف
why did Nie Wenzhi
لماذا فعل ني ونزي
apply lubricating oil on the stairs?
وضع زيت التشحيم على الدرج؟
Song Zhizhi,
أغنية زيزهي،
what exactly do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل بالضبط؟
I've been dependent on my mother for so many years.
لقد كنت أعتمد على والدتي لسنوات عديدة.
How could she hurt me?
كيف يمكنها أن تؤذيني؟
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
do you need me to explain
هل تحتاج مني أن أشرح؟
what exactly happened in this matter?
ماذا حدث بالضبط في هذه المسألة؟
Nie Wenzhi asked Qing to buy lubricating oil,
طلب ني ون تشي من تشينغ شراء زيت التشحيم،
saying it was for home use,
قائلا أنه كان للاستخدام المنزلي،
Qing inadvertently
تشينغ عن غير قصد
saw Nie Wenzhi
رأى ني وينزي
applying lubricating oil on the stairs.
وضع زيت التشحيم على السلالم.
To protect herself,
لحماية نفسها،
she recorded this video.
لقد سجلت هذا الفيديو.
And then you fell,
ثم سقطت
and then you became like this.
وبعدها أصبحت هكذا.
Nie Xiaofei,
ني شياوفى،
can you wake up a bit?
هل يمكنك الاستيقاظ قليلا؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Why? Why would she harm me?
لماذا؟ لماذا تؤذيني؟
She's my biological mother.
إنها أمي البيولوجية.
She can't harm me.
لا يمكنها أن تؤذيني.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Yes.
نعم.
This is the biological mother you think.
هذه هي الأم البيولوجية التي تعتقدينها.
Do you really know her?
هل تعرفها حقا؟
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
[DNA Paternity Test Report] This
[تقرير اختبار الأبوة DNA] هذا
is the mother you think.
هي الأم التي تفكر بها.
Song Zhizhi.
أغنية زيزهي.
Impossible!
مستحيل!
Do you know how she and I
هل تعلم كيف هي وأنا
lived in the family all these years?
عاش في العائلة كل هذه السنوات؟
Do you know how hard it was
هل تعلم كم كان الأمر صعبًا؟
for us to depend on each other?
لكي نعتمد على بعضنا البعض؟
She can't treat me like this.
لا يمكنها أن تعاملني بهذه الطريقة.
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
But I know in this report,
ولكنني أعلم في هذا التقرير،
it is clearly states
إنه ينص بوضوح
that the genetic similarity between her and Yi Wenhan
أن التشابه الجيني بينها وبين يي وين هان
is 99%.
99%.
While with you,
بينما كنت معك،
there is no blood relationship.
لا يوجد علاقة دم.
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
if you don't believe, you can check it again.
إذا كنت لا تصدق، يمكنك التحقق من ذلك مرة أخرى.
I didn't know until I saw this report.
لم أكن أعلم حتى رأيت هذا التقرير.
You're just a pawn.
أنت مجرد بيدق.
Everything she did
كل ما فعلته
was for her biological son, Yi Wenhan.
كان ذلك من أجل ابنها البيولوجي، يي وين هان.
Between you and Yi Wenhan,
بينك وبين يي وينهان،
she never chose you.
انها لم تختارك ابدًا
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
can you wake up a bit?
هل يمكنك الاستيقاظ قليلا؟
Can you think carefully
هل يمكنك التفكير بعناية؟
about who truly treats you well?
من الذي يعاملك جيدًا حقًا؟
How has Dad treated you since you were a child?
كيف كان والدك يعاملك منذ أن كنت طفلاً؟
I've always regarded you as my own biological sister.
لقد اعتبرتك دائمًا بمثابة أختي البيولوجية.
Xiaofei.
شياوفي.
I came by today to tell you all this.
لقد جئت اليوم لأخبركم بكل هذا.
I hope you can see the reality clearly.
أتمنى أن تتمكن من رؤية الواقع بوضوح.
I also think,
انا ايضا اعتقد
if I don't tell you these things today, I will regret it.
إذا لم أخبرك بهذه الأشياء اليوم، فسوف أندم على ذلك.
I feel really bad seeing you like this today.
أشعر بالسوء حقًا لرؤيتك بهذا الشكل اليوم.
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
you have to cheer up.
عليك أن تشعر بالسعادة.
Ji Baijian
جي بيجيان
knows a very capable doctor abroad.
يعرف طبيبًا كفؤًا جدًا في الخارج.
He said there's a high chance of curing your leg.
قال أن هناك فرصة كبيرة لعلاج ساقك.
You might be able to stand up.
ربما تكون قادرا على الوقوف.
Don't worry about the medical expenses,
لا تقلق بشأن النفقات الطبية،
I'll take care of it for you.
سأعتني بهذا الأمر من أجلك.
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
I hope that from today onwards,
آمل أنه من اليوم فصاعدا،
you will no longer be anyone's pawn.
لن تكون بعد الآن بيدقًا لأحد.
You need to take control of your own life.
يجب عليك السيطرة على حياتك الخاصة.
[The maternal sample to be tested can be excluded]
[ يمكن استبعاد العينة الأمومية المراد اختبارها ]
[as the biological mother of the child sample to be tested.]
[باعتبارها الأم البيولوجية لعينة الطفل المراد اختبارها.]
[DNA Identification on the Paternity Relationship]
[تحديد الحمض النووي على أساس علاقة الأبوة]
[between Nie Wenzhi and Nie Xiaofei]
[بين ني وينزي وني شياوفي]
[The maternal sample to be tested can be excluded]
[ يمكن استبعاد العينة الأمومية المراد اختبارها ]
[as the biological mother of the child sample to be tested.]
[باعتبارها الأم البيولوجية لعينة الطفل المراد اختبارها.]
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
please sit down.
من فضلك اجلس.
Thank goodness, you're finally out.
الحمد لله أنك خرجت أخيرا.
Did you suffer any injustice?
هل تعرضت لأي ظلم؟
Mr. Li,
السيد لي،
you've watched me grow up since I was a child.
لقد شاهدتني أكبر منذ أن كنت طفلاً.
You know I would never do that.
أنت تعرف أنني لن أفعل ذلك أبدًا.
It's good that you're fine.
من الجيد أنك بخير.
I asked you out today despite your busy schedule.
لقد طلبت منك الخروج اليوم على الرغم من جدولك المزدحم.
Actually, I want to talk about the project
في الواقع، أريد أن أتحدث عن المشروع
I mentioned to you last time.
لقد ذكرت لك في المرة الماضية.
I hope you can give me some guidance.
آمل أن تتمكن من إعطائي بعض التوجيهات.
I analyzed your project carefully
لقد قمت بتحليل مشروعك بعناية
and verified it with several experts around me.
وتأكدت من ذلك مع العديد من الخبراء من حولي.
They all think highly of your project.
إنهم جميعًا يفكرون بشكل كبير في مشروعك.
So,
لذا،
it has strengthened my resolve to support you.
لقد عززت عزيمتي لدعمك.
Zhizhi, don't worry.
زيزي، لا تقلقي.
My vote at the shareholders' meeting
صوتي في اجتماع المساهمين
will definitely go to you.
سوف أذهب إليك بالتأكيد.
That's great, Mr. Li.
هذا رائع، السيد لي.
I...
أنا...
I'll toast you with tea instead of wine.
سأقدم لك الشاي بدلاً من النبيذ.
Okay!
تمام!
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I will definitely live up to your support for me.
سوف أكون على قدر دعمكم لي بالتأكيد.
Cheers.
هتافات.
[Project Proposal Speech]
[خطاب مقترح المشروع]
Thank you all.
شكرا لكم جميعا.
You did a great job just now.
لقد قمت بعمل عظيم للتو.
It seems you've already got this in the bag.
يبدو أنك حصلت على هذا بالفعل في الحقيبة.
I have tried my best.
لقد حاولت أن أبذل قصارى جهدي.
Everything that can be said is said.
كل ما يمكن أن يقال يقال.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Of course, I'm here to support you.
بالطبع، أنا هنا لدعمك.
I remember Grandma's request.
أتذكر طلب جدتي.
[Starlight Jewelry Shareholders' Mtg] The speeches of the two have concluded.
[اجتماع المساهمين في شركة ستارلايت للمجوهرات] انتهى خطاب الطرفين.
We invite the respected Mr. Li, a shareholder,
ندعو السيد المحترم لي، أحد المساهمين،
to share his opinion.
ليشارك برأيه.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
Ms. Song discussed the plan with me
ناقشت السيدة سونغ الخطة معي
before the shareholders' meeting.
قبل اجتماع المساهمين.
She introduced her ideas and innovations
قدمت أفكارها وإبداعاتها
to me in detail.
لي بالتفصيل.
From the perspective of new media marketing,
من منظور تسويق وسائل الإعلام الجديدة،
it gave me many new insights.
لقد أعطاني العديد من الأفكار الجديدة.
I've always been very optimistic
لقد كنت دائمًا متفائلًا جدًا
about such a courageous and capable person.
عن مثل هذا الشخص الشجاع والقادر.
But as a shareholder,
ولكن بصفتي مساهمًا،
I tend to be more conservative.
أنا أميل إلى أن أكون أكثر تحفظًا.
You just received an email, didn't you?
لقد تلقيت للتو بريدًا إلكترونيًا، أليس كذلك؟
Just for such an email.
فقط لمثل هذا البريد الإلكتروني.
You came to blackmail me.
لقد أتيت لابتزازي.
I truly have your best interests at heart.
أنا حقا لدي أفضل المصالح في القلب.
I hope to nip this matter in the bud.
آمل أن أتمكن من وضع حد لهذه المسألة.
Just get to the point.
فقط الوصول إلى النقطة.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
So I think
لذلك أعتقد
we need an experienced person
نحن بحاجة إلى شخص ذو خبرة
like Yi Wenhan.
مثل يي وينهان.
Although Ms. Song is not as experienced
على الرغم من أن السيدة سونغ ليست ذات خبرة
as Mr. Yi Wenhan,
كما السيد يي وينهان،
but from what I heard from the plan just now,
ولكن مما سمعته من الخطة الآن،
I believe Ms. Song is indeed better
أعتقد أن السيدة سونغ أفضل بالفعل
in terms of innovation.
من حيث الابتكار.
If a company always plays it safe and stays conservative,
إذا كانت الشركة تلعب دائمًا بأمان وتظل محافظة،
sooner or later it will be eliminated by the market.
عاجلا أم آجلا سيتم القضاء عليه من قبل السوق.
Therefore, I think,
لذلك أعتقد،
Ms. Song's Brand Marketing Method,
طريقة تسويق العلامة التجارية للسيدة سونغ،
to a great extent,
إلى حد كبير،
will reverse the current situation.
سوف يعكس الوضع الحالي.
This can only represent your personal opinion.
هذا لا يمكن أن يمثل إلا رأيك الشخصي.
The company and I
الشركة وأنا
have been through ups and downs for more than ten years.
لقد مررت بالصعود والهبوط لأكثر من عشر سنوات.
I saw it develop from a small chain brand
لقد رأيته يتطور من علامة تجارية صغيرة
to what it is today.
إلى ما هو عليه اليوم.
As for the person who is more suitable to represent the company,
أما بالنسبة للشخص الأكثر ملاءمة لتمثيل الشركة،
I have more say than you.
لدي رأي أكثر منك.
It seems there are different opinions.
يبدو أن هناك آراء مختلفة.
In the end, we will decide by voting.
وفي النهاية سوف نقرر عن طريق التصويت.
We will determine the candidate for the agent
سوف نحدد المرشح للوكيل
based on the proportion of shares held
على أساس نسبة الأسهم المملوكة
by the supporters of the candidates.
من قبل مؤيدي المرشحين.
[Final Voting Result: Song Zhizhi, Yi Wenhan]
[نتيجة التصويت النهائية: سونغ زيزي، يي وينهان]
Now,
الآن،
Mr. Yi Wenhan wins by 9 percentage points.
فاز السيد يي وين هان بفارق 9 نقاط مئوية.
You all have seen it.
لقد رأيتم ذلك جميعا.
Mr. Yi Wenhan is now far ahead.
السيد يي وين هان الآن متقدم كثيرًا.
This is sufficient to show
وهذا يكفي لإظهار
shareholders' thoughts and attitudes.
أفكار ومواقف المساهمين.
Now that things have come to this,
الآن وقد وصلت الأمور إلى هذا الحد،
we don't need to waste any more time.
لا نحتاج إلى إضاعة المزيد من الوقت.
Let's announce the result directly.
دعونا نعلن النتيجة مباشرة.
As a shareholder holding 20% of the shares,
باعتباري مساهمًا يمتلك 20% من الأسهم،
I support Ms. Song Zhizhi.
أنا أؤيد السيدة سونغ تشيزي.
Ji Baijian.
جي بيجيان.
Shareholders' meeting of Starlight Jewelry
اجتماع المساهمين في شركة ستارلايت للمجوهرات
does not welcome outsiders.
لا يرحب بالغرباء.
Today's meeting belongs to Ms. Song Zhizhi
الاجتماع اليوم يخص السيدة سونغ تشيزي
and also to my fiancée.
وأيضا لخطيبتي.
Also, the shares of Jihong Group you just mentioned.
وأيضاً أسهم مجموعة جيهونغ التي ذكرتها للتو.
Sorry,
آسف،
when I said I hold 20% of the shares,
عندما قلت أنني أملك 20٪ من الأسهم،
I meant Starlight Jewelry.
أقصد مجوهرات ستارلايت.
His shareholding certificate is valid.
شهادة مساهمته صالحة.
The share ratio is 20%.
نسبة المشاركة هي 20%.
I represent Chairman Ye Taiting of Starlight Jewelry
أنا أمثل رئيس مجلس إدارة شركة ستارلايت للمجوهرات يي تايتينغ
to announce his vote.
ليعلن عن تصويته.
Given Mr. Yi's past management experience
نظراً لخبرة السيد يي الإدارية السابقة
and achievements,
وإنجازاتها،
Mr. Ye supports Mr. Yi Wenhan
السيد يي يدعم السيد يي وينهان
in acting general manager of Starlight Jewelry.
مدير عام بالإنابة لشركة ستارلايت للمجوهرات.
With the shares he holds,
مع الأسهم التي يملكها،
he supports Mr. Yi Wenhan.
إنه يدعم السيد يي وينهان.
Mr. Ye
السيد يي
supports Mr. Yi Wenhan with 12 percentage points.
ويدعم السيد يي وين هان بـ12 نقطة مئوية.
Yi Wenhan wins by 1 percentage point.
فاز يي وين هان بفارق نقطة مئوية واحدة.
Let's congratulate Mr. Yi Wenhan.
دعونا نهنئ السيد يي وينهان.
Stamp.
ختم.
Stamp!
ختم!
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
After you left yesterday,
بعد أن غادرت أمس،
I have thought a lot.
لقد فكرت كثيرا.
Finally, I figured out the ins and outs
أخيرًا، توصلت إلى التفاصيل
of these matters.
من هذه الأمور.
I know
أنا أعرف
if I don't come here today,
إذا لم آتي إلى هنا اليوم،
I'll regret it all my life.
سأندم على ذلك طيلة حياتي.
I'm here today as a shareholder
أنا هنا اليوم كمساهم
to exercise my rights.
لممارسة حقوقي.
I can do it.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
I believe everyone has recently
أعتقد أن الجميع قد فعلوا ذلك مؤخرًا
heard about my scandal.
سمعت عن فضيحتي.
I'm here today,
انا هنا اليوم
in addition to voting,
بالإضافة إلى التصويت،
and I still want to tell everyone
ومازلت أريد أن أخبر الجميع
to expose the true face of a woman.
لكشف الوجه الحقيقي للمرأة.
Nie Wenzhi,
ني وينزي،
my mom.
أمي.
She made me pretend to be pushed down the stairs by Song Zhizhi
لقد جعلتني أتظاهر بأن سونغ تشيزي يدفعني إلى أسفل الدرج
creating an accident and framing her.
إحداث حادث وتأطيرها.
But in fact,
ولكن في الواقع،
Song Zhizhi didn't push me at all that night.
لم يضغط عليّ سونغ تشيزي على الإطلاق تلك الليلة.
Originally, our plan could have been completed easily.
في الأصل، كان من الممكن أن تكتمل خطتنا بسهولة.
But unexpectedly,
ولكن بشكل غير متوقع،
my mother
والدتي
actually applied lubricating oil all over the stairs herself.
في الواقع، قامت بوضع زيت التشحيم على جميع أنحاء الدرج بنفسها.
I guess
اعتقد
it's because she had already sensed
هذا لأنها شعرت بالفعل
that I didn't want to be controlled by her anymore
أنني لم أعد أرغب في أن أسيطر عليها بعد الآن
and to do things against my will.
والقيام بأشياء ضد إرادتي.
So tell me,
فأخبرني
is all this true?
هل كل هذا صحيح؟
Mom.
أم.
Nie Xiaofei, are you crazy?
ني زياوفي، هل أنت مجنون؟
Did you hurt your head?
هل أذيت رأسك؟
You come here and talk nonsense!
أنت تأتي هنا وتتحدث هراء!
Get out of here.
اخرج من هنا.
Let her speak.
دعها تتحدث.
There are more ridiculous things.
هناك أشياء أكثر سخافة.
My mother
والدتي
is not my mom at all.
ليست أمي على الإطلاق
The appraisal report shows
ويظهر تقرير التقييم
that I have no parent-child relationship with her at all.
أنه ليس لدي أي علاقة أب أو أم معها على الإطلاق.
Her real child
طفلها الحقيقي
is Yi Wenhan.
هو يي وينهان.
So today's shareholder meeting
لذا اجتماع المساهمين اليوم
is used by her to seize power
تستخدمها للاستيلاء على السلطة
for her real child.
من أجل طفلها الحقيقي.
Xiaofei,
شياوفي،
don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث هراء.
So many years,
منذ سنوات عديدة،
I've done a lot of things wrong.
لقد فعلت الكثير من الأشياء الخاطئة.
Although sometimes I was bewitched and used.
على الرغم من أنني في بعض الأحيان كنت مسحورة ومستغلة.
But wrong is wrong.
ولكن الخطأ هو الخطأ.
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
for my previous mistakes.
لأخطائي السابقة.
I don't expect everyone to forgive me,
لا أتوقع من الجميع أن يسامحوني،
But today I dare to say it,
ولكن اليوم أجرؤ على أن أقول ذلك،
I have a clear conscience.
لدي ضمير مرتاح.
In my life,
في حياتي،
when I was most confused and helpless,
عندما كنت في أشد حالات الارتباك والعجز،
Song Zhizhi helped me regardless of past grudges.
لقد ساعدني سونغ تشيزي بغض النظر عن ضغائن الماضي.
She let me know
لقد اخبرتني
my own life
حياتي الخاصة
shouldn't be controlled by others.
لا ينبغي أن يتم التحكم بها من قبل الآخرين.
So I'd rather give up everything
لذلك أفضل أن أتخلى عن كل شيء
to be a decent person.
أن يكون شخصًا لائقًا.
I decide
انا قررت
to use my 2% equity
لاستخدام 2٪ من حقوق الملكية الخاصة بي
to support my sister,
لدعم أختي،
Song Zhizhi.
أغنية زيزهي.
♪From this moment on, I no longer care♪
♪من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا، لم أعد أهتم♪
♪No more noise in my ears♪
♪لا مزيد من الضوضاء في أذني♪
♪That's the peace I've always yearned for♪
♪هذا هو السلام الذي كنت أشتاق إليه دائمًا♪
♪Who was I trying to change for?♪
♪من كنت أحاول التغيير من أجله؟♪
♪Smiling, crying, complaining♪
♪يبتسم، يبكي، يشكو♪
♪That's the contentment I should learn to embrace♪
♪هذا هو الرضا الذي يجب أن أتعلم احتضانه♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪How many times you've hurt me♪
♪كم مرة جرحتني♪
♪What you call sincere devotion♪
♪ما تسميه التفاني الصادق♪
♪Maybe I've just grown numb♪
♪ربما أصبحت مخدرًا للتو♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪Even if I've strayed♪
♪حتى لو ضللت الطريق♪
♪I'm still crying for someone♪
♪مازلت أبكي من أجل شخص ما♪
♪Crying over losing to my own pride♪
♪ البكاء على الخسارة أمام كبريائي ♪